<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>linux on Ceso Adventures</title>
    <link>https://ceso.github.io/tags/linux/</link>
    <description>Recent content in linux on Ceso Adventures</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2020 02:30:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ceso.github.io/tags/linux/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hacking/OSCP cheatsheet</title>
      <link>https://ceso.github.io/posts/2020/04/hacking/oscp-cheatsheet/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2020 02:30:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ceso.github.io/posts/2020/04/hacking/oscp-cheatsheet/</guid>
      <description>Hacking/OSCP Cheatsheet Well, just finished my 90 days journey of OSCP labs, so now here is my cheatsheet of it (and of hacking itself), I will be adding stuff in an incremental way as I go having time and/or learning new stuff. But this is basically the tools I tend to relie and use in this way the most. Hope is helpfull for you!
Enumeration Network sniffing (using NMAP) I tend to run 3 nmaps, an initial one, a full one and an UDP one, all of them in parallel:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hack The Box - AI</title>
      <link>https://ceso.github.io/posts/2020/02/hack-the-box-ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ceso.github.io/posts/2020/02/hack-the-box-ai/</guid>
      <description>Quick Summary Finally, I&amp;rsquo;m posting the walk-through of this box, currently, I&amp;rsquo;m preparing my OSCP so most of my free time goes dedicated to it :D. At the time I did this box, I was only documenting with screenshots, so some dates could differ between the write up below as I accessed now to get plain text to not overload this with screenshots.
This was a box where for the foothold, you needed to upload a .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hack The Box - Bitlab</title>
      <link>https://ceso.github.io/posts/2020/01/hack-the-box-bitlab/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ceso.github.io/posts/2020/01/hack-the-box-bitlab/</guid>
      <description>Quick Summary First than everything, I need to make clear that this box has 2 ways for doing privilege escalation: one is doing reversing and the other taking advantage of a misconfiguration with sudo and git. I will describe the steps for the sudo + git path as I&amp;rsquo;m just starting to do my first steps into more low-level stuff. Despite this, in the future I will actualize this post to reflect also the reversing path.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hack The Box - Craft</title>
      <link>https://ceso.github.io/posts/2020/01/hack-the-box-craft/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ceso.github.io/posts/2020/01/hack-the-box-craft/</guid>
      <description>Quick Summary So!! Today was just retired Craft from Hack the box, this was a really fun box to do, and also I felt pretty well doing it, because even if I needed some nudges, it was actually the first box I got to the foothold without hints (elsen if I needed some guidance with python, thanks a lot @Frundrod!!), and afterward to get user I was a bit lost and also needed some hints (was not realizing something I have literally in my nose, thankss a lot @Fugl!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>